How to sell your home without a broker - 7 steps.
1. Evaluate the home.
Check out what similar housing in the same area has been sold for-
-Or ask some brokers to make a free valuation.
You can also hire a valuation person.
However, it costs money.
2. Make a sales ad.
Try to formulate you as a real broker.
Add nice pictures to the home.
Ask family and friends to spread your ad on social media-
4. Arrange view.
Make the home ready to be shown.
Keep in mind that more than one show may be required.
Don't miss out on contact details to speculator-
-So that you can contact me after the show.
5. Bidding.
Contact the speculators and hear if anyone wants to place a bid.
Keep them updated on bids coming in.
You decide to whom you want to sell and what price you accept.
6. Check the buyer's finances.
Ask to see proof that the buyer has the funding clear-